cart66.com 2019-04-11

# Privacy Policy | WordPress Shopping Cart

**PRIVACY NOTICE**  
We understand and respect your concerns about privacy. Please read our privacy policy before using the Website. It indicates the information we collect and actions we take to secure any personal information you may choose to provide while using the site, as well as how we collect it and use it. www.cart66.com does not share any of this information with other parties.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
By using the Website, you may provide us with information about yourself such as name, address, phone and email or other information you may choose to provide. By visiting this Website, you may automatically provide data such as your Internet protocol address, Internet service provider, operating system, the Website from which you arrived, and the time and date as functions of the software operation of this Site.

**COOKIES**  
A cookie is a small file that is downloaded onto your computer when you visit the Website. The file collects information about how you navigate the site in order to help us facilitate your visit and gain valuable information about how best to serve you. You may choose to have your computer prompt you whenever the Website attempts to send you a cookie, or disable cookies if you prefer to through your browser window.

**REGISTRATION AND PASSWORDS**  
Registration is not required to gain access to the Website, but there are portions of the Site that require a password. Do not reveal your password to other parties and please remember that the software is case sensitive.

**DELETED DATA**  
Users can request to delete their data from our system at any time.  This will include their own personal information, as well as all of the customer information they have stored in their account for others.  In addition, their data will be removed from our backups after 7 days.

**QUESTIONS?**  
If you have any questions or concerns at all, please feel free to reach out to our [support team](https://cart66.com/support/), who will be happy to assist you.
